[{"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 30, "question": "I mean, but is it like all things in comedy, especially those running things, is it the simpler the idea, often, the more effective it is?", "qSentId": 29}, {"answer": "Oh, my gosh!", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "Who are you most likely to write a thank you note to right now as a comedian -- Anthony Weiner or Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "Both have been great to me.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "Tough, right?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "ALLON: It's the best for us.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 62, "question": "But for you guys, I mean, brilliant, isn't it?", "qSentId": 61}, {"answer": "But instinctively your protective shield is comedy.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "I honestly, purposely have not gone to therapy because I know some crazy stuff's going to be dragged up and, you know, I'll be like, wait, what?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "No, I mean, I guess it is.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "You don't really want to answer that question, do you?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "The tomorrow show, yes, exactly.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 113, "question": "How can \"The Tonight Show\" start tomorrow?", "qSentId": 112}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "Why weren't you that popular?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "Were you drawn to the absurd and the potentially comedic always?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "I mean, yes, you don't have to.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "I don't -- wasn't anybody drive in New York anyway?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "It was so happy.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 160, "question": "Did you have a happy childhood?", "qSentId": 159}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "Did you?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "The striped shirt.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 210, "question": "And apart from the hair, which was outrageous -- what do you think when you watch that?", "qSentId": 209}, {"answer": "I think that was the thing.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "Did you love that buzz of laughter coming from people?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "At some stage in my life, I can do that with you.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 268, "question": "And we asked Brian if he would do it just Brian Williams and he, you know?", "qSentId": 267}, {"answer": "I think it was like -- you know, I actually auditioned for the show -- I dropped out of school -- college and I went to L.A. to join the Gramlings (ph) which is like the second city of L.A. like improv troupe and learned how to act and act with other people, because when you do standup comedy you don't know how to act with other people because you're on stage by yourself.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "When you actually discovered you had the possibility of being on it, what was that moment like for you?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "Well, you know, you start a show -- a publicist, you know, they control the actors, what publicity they do.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "Why would you do that?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "I like -- of course, I love comedians, any comedian.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "What really makes you laugh?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "British humor.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "What kind of things?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "I do, yes, yes.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "You know those guys?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "I think that's my thing.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "And that's your trademark, I think, isn't it?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "He's a smart, smart businessman.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "I mean, indisputably, he's endlessly entertaining, isn't he, in all guises?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "It's almost like watching like your family fight.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "So, when you get a situation that arose in the way that it did and it creates this awful chasm between them, how do you feel about that?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "ALLON: I don't know.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 515, "question": "Where do you think the real problem lay in all that?", "qSentId": 514}, {"answer": "I think that's bizarre in the first place.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 518, "question": "Was it -- was it as simple as when Jay was number one, NBC saying to him, you've got five more years, then you have to stop, without thinking in five years' time you might still be number one?", "qSentId": 517}, {"answer": "No, I don't blame Jay.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "Do you blame Jay for anything that happened?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "I don't think I have the look for it, to be honest, to be a leading man.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "Are you a frustrated movie star because you've got the kind of looks for it and you've had a standup movie?", "qSentId": 551}, {"answer": "I don't like it.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "What I find odd about standup comedians or anyone who's done that is how you ever have the patience for movies?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "I got this report that I have to do for next Friday.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 595, "question": "What you working on there dude?", "qSentId": 594}, {"answer": "Sheen.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 600, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 599}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 612, "question": "I mean, hard work because these sketches aren't easy to do, are they?", "qSentId": 611}, {"answer": "Adonis DNA.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 621, "question": "Is he winning?", "qSentId": 620}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "Is any part of what's happened with Charlie winning, do you think?", "qSentId": 622}, {"answer": "Drinking I think is probably the closest I've come to doing anything.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 638, "question": "Have you had a moment in your life -- not Charlie Sheen- esque, but have you ever got into boozing, drugs, any of the kind of pitfalls that follow comedians, entertainers?", "qSentId": 637}, {"answer": "Bruce Springsteen.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 646, "question": "What's been the most excited you've been about a guest that's come on your show?", "qSentId": 645}, {"answer": "I don't believe in that thing you should never meet your heroes.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 655, "question": "Was he great in real life?", "qSentId": 654}, {"answer": "I'd be nothing without my wife.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 744, "question": "Your wife?", "qSentId": 743}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 774, "question": "Is she a good critic of your -- of your work?", "qSentId": 773}, {"answer": "She lives in New York.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 782, "question": "Does she live there?", "qSentId": 781}, {"answer": "I called her.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 797, "question": "Do you find it funny?", "qSentId": 796}, {"answer": "I mean, there might be some right now.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 818, "question": "Can we expect any little Fallons on the way?", "qSentId": 817}, {"answer": "It's impossible.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 833, "question": "How would you feel if you had a child with no sense of humor?", "qSentId": 832}, {"answer": "Well, I feel unnerved by this, but I'll do it.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 881, "question": "Do you mind?", "qSentId": 880}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 901, "question": "You sure about that?", "qSentId": 900}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110615pmt", "aSentId": 913, "question": "Can you do what you're good at, please?", "qSentId": 912}]